4degreez.com 2017-06-19

# 4degreez.com Media Kit

Home

**This document describes the ways in which 4degreez.com respects visitor privacy.**

Our server logs the visitor's IP address and certain browser headers as part of the standard logging proccess that most web sites follow. This data is stored only in log form and is used to generate aggregate reports on visitor use of the site. Information such as real names and e-mail addresses are not collected by simply visiting 4degreez.com, and in fact are not possible to collect without a visitor actually volunteering that information.

We may collect personal information volunteered by the visitor through the use of HTML forms, and this might include surveys, site registrations, or other form posts. Any personal contact information that is volunteered by a visitor is not shared with any third parties.

All quizzes hosted on 4degreez.com are competely anonymous, and the results are not linked to the quiz taker.

Using 4degreez.com may result in a cookie being set, which is used to "remember" you from page to page. This is the essential function of HTTP cookies. In this case, it allows you to be logged in during your visit.

To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our web pages. As a result of your visit to 4degreez.com, ad server companies may collect information such as your browser headers, IP address, whether you have Flash or javascript enabled, and clickstream. Advertisers may also use web beacons or set cookies. to collect this information (which is in turn used to tailor advertisements to you), as well as monitor clicks and credit commissions. Google's DoubleClick uses cookies (called DART cookies) to serve ads specific to you and your interests ("interest based targeting"). The ads displayed will be chosen based on your previous browsing history. This does not rely on personally identifying information and does not track such information. You can opt-out of this specific ad serving on all sites that use it by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx

It is possible for you to disable the cookie feature in your browser by consulting your browser's "help" screen and following the directions. Different browsers offer different methods of blocking cookies. For further information on the privacy policies of our advertisers, consult the following URLs:

http://www.cj.com/privacy.jsp  
http://www.google.com/privacy.html

From time to time, we may use visitor information for new, unanticipated reasons not previously disclosed in our privacy policy. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will update this document to reflect the changes. It is your responsibility to check this document for updates. Changes to our privacy policy will not retroactively affect any data collected.

If this policy is unclear in any way, you may request clarification by sending an e-mail to the address listed below.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated privacy policy, you may contact us at the address below.

We can be reached via e-mail at: four(underscore)degreez(at)yahoo.com
